adflyer.co.uk 2014-02-09

# adflyer: UKs Fastest Growing Marketplace, Where Smarter People Buy & Sell

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.adflyer.co.uk (the Website). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use the Website, posting adverts and other material or contacting us. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with the Website. 
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. 
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and other communication data and the resources that you access.

**  
IP Addresses and Cookies**[](about:blank)  
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our trade users. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns.  
For the same reason, we may obtain information about your usage of the Website by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern. 
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests. 
  * To speed up your searches. 
  * To recognise you when you return to our site. 

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when   
you log on to our site.

**Information gathered by the eBay** **importer**  
The information gathered from eBay is to enable us to create your shopwindow and link your adflyer account to eBay. This information may include but is not limited to: username, email address, feedback, items for sale. We do not gather or store your  eBay password.

**  
Where We Store Your Personal Data**[](about:blank)  
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.  
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.  
**  
Uses Made of the Information**[](about:blank)  
We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us. 
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so. 
  * To notify you about changes to our service. 

We may also use your data to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you.   
We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our business users, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users.  
**  
Disclosure of Your Information**[](about:blank)  
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. 
  * If adflyer Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. 
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Website terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of adflyer Limited, our customers, or others. 
  * Where personal information is provided in respect of an advert.  Where this is the case data (including any personal data in the advert) is shared with third parties with whom adflyer contracts and adverts may appear on websites with whom adflyer has arrangements.   If you have any questions about where the advert will appear please [contact adflyer](http://www.adflyer.co.uk/contact/default.asp)

**Your Rights**[](about:blank)  
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time please [contact adflyer](http://www.adflyer.co.uk/contact/default.asp)

The Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Access to Information**[](about:blank)  
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee permitted by the Act (currently £10) to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.  
**  
Changes to Our Data Protection and Privacy Policy**[](about:blank)  
Any changes we may make to our data protection and privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.  
**  
Contact**[](about:blank)  
Questions, comments and requests regarding this data protection and privacy policy are welcomed and you should please contact adflyer.
